# ARINZE CHRIS

WEB/MOBILE DEVELOPER

# **PERSONAL PROFILE**

Am a skilled Software Developer with over 5 years of experience in software development. If you are looking for a highly skilled and rich mobile/web developer with robust knowledge, a professional attitude, a fast learner, creative, hardworking, excellent communications skills, able to implement UI's, and great in code quality. Then I am the one you are looking for. Over the last five years I have written codes in various languages like C++, Java, Javascript. I have experience in various apps developed in Flutter and React. Experience in both the interface and backend of mobile and web apps. Am always a principled person always paying attention to details, prioritizing quality and being honest.

# **SKILLS**

#### • Front end Development



#### • Mobile Development



#### Blockchain and Web3

Solidity Metamask Hardhat DApps Thirdweb Ethereum

#### • Backend and Database

PHP Laravel
Node js MongoDB
Firebase Sanity.io
Java MySql

C++

UI/UX Design

**Adobe XD** 

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Android Developer (Google Developers and Andela)
- Fundamentals of digital marketing (Google)

# **GET IN CONTACT**

**22** +234-814-659-6444

www.github.com/arinzehills

9

Jos, Nigeria

arinzehill@gmail.com

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### WEB/MOBILE DEVELOPER MOTIV8 TECH LTD

April2021- Nov 2021

 Responsible in development of mobile apps in Flutter and creating web apps powered by Laravel and React.

# FREELANCE WEB AND MOBILE DEVELOPER 2017–2022 some projects and roles:

#### MOBILE/WEB DEVELOPER, BUY ENERGY

- Take part in planning, wire framing and designing the user interface for both the web and mobile application. Which is a platform for paying utility bills.
- Implemented the user interface with Flutter/Dart for mobile and React JS for the front end.
- Responsible for development of API's using Laravel and full integration.

#### MOBILE/WEB DEVELOPER, BRAVELITE LTD

April 2022- Present

- Take part in planning, wire framing and designing the user interface for both the web and mobile application.
- Implemented the user interface with Flutter/Dart for mobile and React is for the web apps .
- Responsible for development of API's using Laravel and full integration.

#### OTHERS

- · Developed a school fee verification mobile app with flutter,
- Developed e-commerce sites, other platforms with react js
- Developed web3 projects built on top of Ethereum for sending and receiving tokens with Solidity, Hardhart with React and next js.

#### **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY | INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY (INVIEW 2022)

FEDERAL UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY MINNA